
import { SportDefinition } from '../../types';

export const lacrosse: SportDefinition = {
    id: 'lacrosse',
    label: 'Lacrosse',
    cuts: {
        mens: {
            jersey: {
                shape: {
                    front: "M140 20 C170 30 230 30 260 20 L380 80 L350 120 L320 100 L320 480 L80 480 L80 100 L50 120 L20 80 L140 20 Z",
                    back: "M140 20 C170 25 230 25 260 20 L380 80 L350 120 L320 100 L320 480 L80 480 L80 100 L50 120 L20 80 L140 20 Z",
                },
                trim: {
                    front: "M140 20 C170 50 230 50 260 20 L250 15 C220 40 180 40 150 15 Z M20 80 L50 120 L60 115 L30 75 Z M380 80 L350 120 L340 115 L370 75 Z",
                    back: "M140 20 C170 25 230 25 260 20 L250 15 C220 20 180 20 150 15 Z"
                }
            },
            shorts: {
                shape: {
                    front: "M80 50 L90 60 C95 120 100 200 105 280 L105 380 C105 400 110 420 120 430 L130 440 L170 440 L180 430 C185 420 185 400 185 380 L185 280 C190 200 195 120 200 60 L210 60 C215 120 220 200 215 280 L215 380 C215 400 215 420 220 430 L230 440 L270 440 L280 430 C290 420 295 400 295 380 L295 280 C300 200 305 120 310 60 L320 50 L80 50 Z",
                    back: "M80 50 L90 60 C95 120 100 200 105 280 L105 380 C105 400 110 420 120 430 L130 440 L170 440 L180 430 C185 420 185 400 185 380 L185 280 C190 200 195 120 200 60 L210 60 C215 120 220 200 215 280 L215 380 C215 400 215 420 220 430 L230 440 L270 440 L280 430 C290 420 295 400 295 380 L295 280 C300 200 305 120 310 60 L320 50 L80 50 Z"
                },
                trim: {
                    front: "M80 50 L320 50 L320 70 L80 70 Z M105 280 L105 290 L185 290 L185 280 Z M215 280 L215 290 L295 290 L295 280 Z",
                    back: "M80 50 L320 50 L320 70 L80 70 Z M105 280 L105 290 L185 290 L185 280 Z M215 280 L215 290 L295 290 L295 280 Z"
                }
            }
        },
        womens: {
            jersey: {
                shape: {
                    front: "M120 20 C150 30 250 30 280 20 L320 40 C320 40 290 160 310 260 C320 300 320 480 320 480 L80 480 C80 480 80 300 90 260 C110 160 80 40 80 40 L120 20 Z",
                    back: "M140 20 C160 20 240 20 260 20 L300 40 C280 100 300 200 320 260 C330 300 320 480 320 480 L80 480 C80 480 70 300 80 260 C100 200 120 100 100 40 L140 20 Z",
                },
                trim: {
                    front: "M120 20 C150 50 250 50 280 20 L270 15 C240 40 160 40 130 15 Z M80 40 C110 160 90 260 90 260 L100 260 C100 260 120 160 90 30 Z M320 40 C290 160 310 260 310 260 L300 260 C300 260 280 160 310 30 Z",
                    back: "M140 20 L260 20 L250 25 L150 25 Z M100 40 C120 100 100 200 80 260 L90 260 C110 200 130 100 110 35 Z M300 40 C280 100 300 200 320 260 L310 260 C290 200 270 100 290 35 Z"
                }
            },
            shorts: {
                shape: {
                    front: "M90 50 L100 60 C105 120 110 200 115 280 L115 370 C115 390 120 410 130 420 L140 430 L175 430 L185 420 C190 410 190 390 190 370 L190 280 C195 200 200 120 200 60 L210 60 C210 120 215 200 210 280 L210 370 C210 390 210 410 215 420 L225 430 L260 430 L270 420 C280 410 285 390 285 370 L285 280 C290 200 295 120 300 60 L310 50 L90 50 Z",
                    back: "M90 50 L100 60 C105 120 110 200 115 280 L115 370 C115 390 120 410 130 420 L140 430 L175 430 L185 420 C190 410 190 390 190 370 L190 280 C195 200 200 120 200 60 L210 60 C210 120 215 200 210 280 L210 370 C210 390 210 410 215 420 L225 430 L260 430 L270 420 C280 410 285 390 285 370 L285 280 C290 200 295 120 300 60 L310 50 L90 50 Z"
                },
                trim: {
                    front: "M90 50 L310 50 L310 70 L90 70 Z M115 280 L115 290 L190 290 L190 280 Z M210 280 L210 290 L285 290 L285 280 Z",
                    back: "M90 50 L310 50 L310 70 L90 70 Z M115 280 L115 290 L190 290 L190 280 Z M210 280 L210 290 L285 290 L285 280 Z"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    templates: [
        {
            id: 'classic',
            label: 'Classic',
            layers: []
        },
        {
            id: 'speed',
            label: 'Speed',
            layers: [
                {
                    id: 'sides',
                    label: 'Side Panels',
                    paths: {
                        jersey: {
                            front: "M80 300 L80 480 L110 480 L110 310 Z M320 300 L320 480 L290 480 L290 310 Z",
                            back: "M80 300 L80 480 L110 480 L110 310 Z M320 300 L320 480 L290 480 L290 310 Z",
                        },
                        shorts: {
                            front: "M80 60 L85 70 L90 280 L95 380 L100 430 L105 430 L110 380 L105 280 L100 70 L95 60 Z M305 60 L300 70 L295 280 L290 380 L295 430 L300 430 L305 380 L310 280 L315 70 L320 60 Z",
                            back: "M80 60 L85 70 L90 280 L95 380 L100 430 L105 430 L110 380 L105 280 L100 70 L95 60 Z M305 60 L300 70 L295 280 L290 380 L295 430 L300 430 L305 380 L310 280 L315 70 L320 60 Z",
                        }
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
};
